smsbag.com 2013-03-15

# smsBAG - SMS Gateway...your No1 SMS link to the World

### Privacy Policy

**General**  
smsbag Privacy Policy covers the collection and use of personal information that is collected by smsbag when you visit our website and register to receive our guide. Your privacy is a priority for smsbag, and we go to great heights to protect it.

**Protection of Database Information**  
Any information sent to smsbag for sms messaging and or storage purposes will remain the property of the account holder. smsbag will at no time collect or redistribute this information without your consent, except where legally required by law to do so. This is with particular reference to any database, numbers and/or recipient details that you may deliver to us, or store on our databases. 

**Situations when smsbag will disclose your information?**

smsbag will disclose your personal data to any other third party with your consent, only if:

* It is required by law,  
* It is necessary in order to provide you with a service which you have requested,  
* We suspect that your use of smsbag services is in breach of their terms of use,  
* To protect the smsbag rights or property, or any smsbag customer,  
* To lessen a serious threat to a person's health or safety.

**The Use of the Information we collected**  
We use information which you provide us to keep track of the smsbag services you have signed up to receive. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyse site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customise our site's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We use your email address to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news from time to time. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. 

**How smsbag stores your information and keeps it secure**

smsbag will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information it holds about you and to keep this information accurate and up to date. Your information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services linked to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by smsbag. However, smsbag will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information. For more information about our privacy practices, you can send us an e-mail or write to us.  

### smsbag Terms and Conditions 

The following are the terms and conditions for use of the smsbag Service ("smsbag Service" or "the Service") by any customer (hereinafter referred to as "the User").

**IMPORTANT** : In terms of section 11 of the Electronic Communications and Transactions (ECT) Act 25 of 2002 and the common law of contract, these terms and conditions are valid binding and enforceable against all persons that access the smsbag website, web pages or any part thereof. If you do not agree to be bound by these terms and conditions you may not use the smsbag website. Reasonable use of the smsbag website shall automatically bound the user to this agreement.

**Use of the website and warranty:**

The information supplied in this website is intended for strictly informational use. It is not binding and might be subject to changes without notice.

smsbag attempts to be as efficient as possible, however smsbag doesn't warrant that the services description as described on the web pages are accurate, complete, reliable or error-free.

smsbag makes neither representations nor warranties of any kind, expressed or implied, as for the operation of these web pages and/or about the information, content, materials, or products included in these web pages. You expressly agree that the use of this site is at your sole risk.

smsbag doesn't warrant that the website and its servers are free from viruses or other harmful components. smsbag will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the access and the use of the site.

**Price Changes**

smsBAG has the right to adjust her prices at any time without any notification to the users. Thus, Prices are flexible and changes as the market price changes

**Intellectual property:**

The information supplied in this website is smsbag sole property and copyright.

The reproduction, duplication, distribution, publication, modification, copying or translation of any of the material contained in this website for commercial purposes without the express authorization of smsbag is strictly prohibited. Counterfeiting shall be pursued.

**Refund Policy:**

Payments are return within 24 hours in case of excess payments or Payment Gateway over charge

Contact: [legal@smsbag.com](mailto:legal@smsbag.com).
